Guide to the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932 -1950
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932-1950
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932-1950
24-01-120
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean
19.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and subject files compiled by the Office of the Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine during William A. Hagan's tenure as dean.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
William A. Hagan was the fourth Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine. His term ran from 1932-1959. Hagan also served on the administrative committee that governed the college from 1931-1932, after the death of the third dean, Pierre A. Fish. Also on that committee were Drs. Earl Sunderville and Raymond Russel Birch. Professor Myron G. Fincher served as Acting Dean from 1943-1944 while Dean Hagan was in Germany
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and subject files compiled by the Office of the Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine during William A. Hagan's tenure as dean. Hagan served as dean from 1932-1959, but the most recent material in this collection only dates to1950, so additional material may be located in the future and added to the collection. Some information about the intervening years may be found in collection # 24-01-1646, New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1959-1974.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hagan, William Arthur, 1893-1963.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
RMC Collection # 24-01-1646, New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1959-1974
RMC Collection #s 24-1-482 amd 24-1-1516, William A. Hagan Papers.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Organized in several chronological series based on the original order of the collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. 1932-1935
Boxes: 1-2, 19
Series II. 1937-1939
Boxes 2-5, 19
Series III. 1939-1941
Boxes 5-6
Series IV. 1940-1942
Boxes: 6-9, 19
Series V. 1942-1943
Boxes: 9-10
Series VI. 1943-1947
Boxes: 10-14, 19
Series VII. 1947-1950
Boxes: 14-18, 20
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. 1932-1935
  - A, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bloomer Bros. Company, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Harrison V., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baldwin, Charles H., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Becton, Dickinson & Co., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Betten, Cornelius, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Birch, R.R., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bostwick, C.D., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breed, Robert S., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Burdick, C.K., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - B (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - B (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cady, B.J., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Communications, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Crane & McGlenen, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cushing, E.R., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - C (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - C (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dunning Letters, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - D (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - D (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Relief Fund, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - E, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Farrand, President Livingstone, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - F (Folder 1 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - F (Folder 2 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - F (Folder 3 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Graves, Mark, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - G, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ho - Hz, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hechscher Fund, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hollingworth, W.G., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Hopkins, G.S., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ha - Ho (Folder 1 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ha - Ho (Folder 2 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ha - Ho (Folder 3 of 3), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - I, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - J, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Kelly, William H., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kerr, A.T., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - K, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Laboratory Products, Inc., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - L (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - L (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mc-Intire and Misc., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - McNeil, J.H., ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - M (Folder 1 of 4), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - M (Folder 2 of 4), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - M (Folder 3 of 4), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - M (Folder 4 of 4), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mc, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - N, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - O, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Parker, G. Thatcher, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Poultry (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Poultry (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Provost A.R. Mann, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - P, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - P, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Q, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Q, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - R, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - S, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - T, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - V, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - W, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Series II. 1937-1939
  - Aa - Al, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Am - Az, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Baker, D.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Boyd, W.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Boy Scout Material, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bradford, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bramhall, Deane Co., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bray, Harry A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Breed, Frank, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Breed, R.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Brooks, Paul B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Brown, Albert L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Brown, J.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Brownell, S.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brumley, O.V., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bruner, D.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Brunett, E.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bullard, J.F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ba - Be, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Be - Bl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Ba - Bl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bm - Bz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bo, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cameron, Hugh S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Campbell, D.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Carpenter, Cliff D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Carpenter, C.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Christmas Letter, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Civil Service, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Clark, W.A. Jr., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Coffin, Foster, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cohran, J.R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committees, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Conference, Jan. 12-13, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conroe, Irwin A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Corbin, C.I., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cotton, Charles E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Curran, Dr. J.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ca - Ce, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ca - Cl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cn - Cz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dahlberg, A.C., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Danks, A.G., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Davis & Geck, Inc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - DeCamp, C.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Desmond, Senator Thomas C., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dick, G.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Difco Laboratories, Inc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Dimock, W.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Division of Motion Pictures, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Donham, C.R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Doris, A.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dukes, H.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dean R.R. Dykstra, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Da - Dh, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Da - Dh, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Di - Dy, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Dm - Dz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Eastman, E.R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Eichorn, Adolph, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - E, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Faculty, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Faculty A.V.M.A. Data, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fanslau, C.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Faulder, E.T., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Fehr, F.F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Feldman, William H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - H.L. Field - Education Department, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Fincher, M.G., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Fitch, C.P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Foster, E.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Frank, George S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Freshmen, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Frick, E.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Frost, J.N., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Fuller, H.K., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - F, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Fa - Fi, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fl - Fz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ga - Gl Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Gage, Simon H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Gannett, R.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Garbutt, Raymond J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Gibson, A.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Gilman, H.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Giltner, Ward, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Gordon, Ruth, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Goss, L.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Graham, Edward K., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Graham, Robert, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Graves, Frank P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Greenlee, Col. C.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ga - Gl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Gm - Gz Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Haight, H.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hallman, E.T., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Hamilton, H.J. Education Dept., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hardenburgh, J.G., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Haring, C.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Harris, C.W. Jr., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Harrison, Ralph A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Hastings, E.G., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Haugaard, William E. - State Architect, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Haupin, G.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Haver-Glover Laboratories, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hayden, C.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hayden, Frank S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Heads of Departments, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Heisler, Charles B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hendershott, R.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hendrickson, J.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Henry, Harry J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hertel, J.P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Heylar, F.G., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hilbert, K.F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Holford, F.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hopper, Earl B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Horner, H.H., Education Dept., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hoskins, H. Preston, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hotels, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hucker, G.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hurt, L.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hutt, F.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ha - Hd, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - He - Hl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hu - Hz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ingmand, Eugene B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - I Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Jakeman, H.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, S.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Jordan, John Jr., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Juniors, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - J Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Kelser, R.A. (Colonel), ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - King, A.C., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Kinkeldey, Otto, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kinney, James R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Knapp, H.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Ka - Kl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Km - Kz Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Lacroix, J.V., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Dean C.E. Ladd, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Lederle Laboratories, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Dr. H.B. Leonard, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Leonard, H.K., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Levine, P.P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Linch Charles, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Loomis, Milton E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - La - Ll, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Lm - Lz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Mackellar, R.S. Jr., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Marsteller, R.P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Maynard, L.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Mayo, N.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - McKim, Orvill E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Mc Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Mead, James M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Meek, H.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Meigs, R.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Merchant, I.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Merck &Co., Inc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Merillat, L.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Merry, A.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Milks, H.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Millar, Joseph A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Miller, A.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Miller, Frank H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Miller, Fred W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Miller, John F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Mohler, J.R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Monroe, Dean B.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Moore, E.V., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Moore, L.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Morris, E.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Morris, Fred B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Morris, M.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Morrison, F.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Murray, Charles, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Ma - Md, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Me - Ml Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Mm - Mz Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - N, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Newman, W.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Newsome, I.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - New York World Fair, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Noback, C.V., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Norden Lab., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Noyes, H.V., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - N.Y.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Olafson, Peter, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Olson, Carl Jr., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Oppenheimer, Russell B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - O Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Parker, L.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Patterson, F.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Patterson, Woodford, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Pierce, R.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Pitman Moore Company, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Powell, Whiton, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - P, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Pa - Pl Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pm -Pz Misc, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rabbits etc. for sale, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ranney, A.F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Regan, J.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Reports, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rice, James E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dean F.K. Richtmeyer, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rivers, Thomas M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - G.F. Rogalsky - Treasurer's Office, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rudman, Henry, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ra - Rl Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rm - Rz Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sampson, Jesse, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Schlotthauer, Carl F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Schmidt, A.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Schnelle, George B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Schoening, H.W., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Seniors, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sexauer, Fred H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sherman, J.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Simms, B.T., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Simons, L.R., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Simpson, A.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Smiley, D.F., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Culver, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - State Veterinary Examination Boards, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Stephenson, H.C., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Stubbs, E.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Sunderville, E.S., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Switzer, W.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Syverton, Jerome T., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sa - Sd, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Se - Sh, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Si - Ss, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - St, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Su - Sz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sm - Sz, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Tenbroeck, Carl, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Terwilligar, R.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Thomson, W.M., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Tiedeman, Walter D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Tillou, L.J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Tittsler, Ralph P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Traum, J., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Trousdale, J.B., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Ta - Tl Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Tm - Tz Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Udall, D.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - U Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - V Misc., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Way, Gassius, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Weatherlow, Hugh E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Weatherlow, Hugh E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hon. Abraham S. Weber, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wegner, E.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Wheeler, R.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Wight, A.E., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Will Corporation, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Williams, H.H., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Williams, W.L., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Wilson, I.D., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Winslow, C. - E.A., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Wa - Wd, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - We - Wh, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Zepp, C.P., ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - XYZ, ca. 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Series III. 1939 - 1941
  - Annual Conference 1940, ca. 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Gm - Gz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Ha - Hl, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Hm - Hz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - I, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - I, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - J, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - K, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - La - Ll, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lm -Lz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ma - Ml, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mc, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mm - Mz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nevitt, John, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Na - Nl, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Nm - Nz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - O, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pa - Pl, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pm - Pz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ra - Rl, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Rm - Rz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Sa - Sl (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sa - Sl (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ta - Tl, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Tm - Tz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - U, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - V, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Wa - We, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Wi, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Wm - Wz, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - XYZ, ca. 1939 - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Series IV. 1940-1942
  - A, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Babcock, Howard E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Babson, E.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Baker, James A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Bayne, T.L. Jr., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Bell, Wilson B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Benson, H.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Berry, George P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Betten, Cornelius, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Biological Abstracts, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Birch, Dr. R.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Blau, N.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Boy Scout Material, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Bradford, E.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Bray, Harry A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Breed, Robert S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Brown, A.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Brownell, S.J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Brumley, O.V., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Bullard, J.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - B (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - B (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cameron, H.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Campbell, D.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Carpenter, Cliff D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Carpenter, C.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Civil Service, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Coffin, F.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cohran, J.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Conference, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Conroe, I.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cotton, Chas E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Crossman, E.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - C Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Danks, A.G., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Davis & Geck, Inc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - De Camp, C.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Desmond, T.C., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Dick, G.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dimock, W.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Donham, C.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dukes, H.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dunn, W.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Dunning Letters, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 23)